brought this bastard a coffee here
oh i said
and then he liked the coffee
it's good but ours is better
oh the kid how is he in the key here
oh on the brother ruler
it's us it's us
I'll get there we'll go on this
that will attract the crowd
communication
positioning and the way you talk
because you don't know how to sell the story
nobody will watch
because if you don't promote your cheating brother
don't expect others to promote for you
hi there caio do valeu
I'm here analyzing the crowd's marketing
So One Two
Three take my hand and come with me
Because you look so Fine
that i really wanna make you Mine
Yeah You Got It
tamo together
did not like
are almost
I don't know eight o'clock at night
caraca hand
I got here half a day
I don't know,
it's dark
guy bought my marketing plan
and I was there all day man
and it's really cool
but then I started thinking
I spoke caramba dear
but when we sell our time
we don't have time to do our things
it took me a lot off the road man
when you dedicate your time and effort to working on the
project
from someone
it's the same time and effort you could be dedicating
to work for you
I prefer to work in my dream
than working on someone else's dream
until tomorrow was worth
haha